[
  {
    "question": "wrzeszczeć",
    "answer": "scream"
  },
  {
    "question": "telefon",
    "answer": "phone"
  },
  {
    "question": "kuchnia",
    "answer": "kitchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "płakać",
    "answer": "cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "tańczyć",
    "answer": "dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "samolot",
    "answer": "airplane"
  },
  {
    "question": "jacht",
    "answer": "yacht"
  },
  {
    "question": "biegać",
    "answer": "run"
  },
  {
    "question": "samochód",
    "answer": "car"
  },
  {
    "question": "jeździć",
    "answer": "drive"
  }
]